Guide to the Betty C. Jukes Papers
University of Houston Libraries
Betty C. Jukes Papers
1918-2014
1967-2014
02/2014-008
Jukes, Betty C.
26.00 linear feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
This collection is predominantly comprised of documents related to Betty Jukes’ nearly fifty years as an event planner, philanthropist, and volunteer in Houston. Organizations of note that Mrs. Jukes was involved with include the Houston Junior Woman’s Club, The Woman’s Club of Houston, the Charles A. Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh Fund, and more. Spanning the years of 1967 through 2014, this collection also includes various awards and ephemera that Betty Jukes received throughout her career, and many interesting letters of correspondence between Mrs. Jukes and persons of note such as Lady Bird Johnson and Ima Hogg. Items are filed according to organizational affiliation and year.
Biographical Information:
Betty C. Jukes, originally from Orlando, Florida, moved to Houston in 1967 with her husband, Harry Jukes, in 1967. Betty founded the First Junior Woman’s Club of Houston and the Houston Junior Woman’s Club, of which she was the president from 1968-1969. Betty also served as president of The Woman’s Club of Houston from 1973-1976, where she coordinated a large number of philanthropic events and charity programs. She also coordinated events for the Houston March of Dimes, the Houston School for the Deaf, the Houston Youth Symphony and Ballet, and the Clean Houston Proud Partners Luncheon. Other organizations that Betty has been involved with include the World Wildlife Fund, the Charles A. Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh Memorial Fund, the Mercury Seven Foundation, the Helen and Immanuel Olshan Texas Music Festival, and Friends of the Moores School of Music at the University of Houston, and more.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Charles A. and Anne Morrow Lindbergh Fund; Houston Junior Woman's Club (Houston, Tex.); Woman's Club of Houston (Houston, Tex.)
Genre/Form of Material:
Brochures; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Newsletters; Scrapbooks
Personal Name:
Jukes, Betty C.
Topical Term:
Performing arts; Philanthropists -- Texas
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research
Related Materials:
Auxiliary of the Center for Hearing and Speech Records
Information about related materials is available at http://archon.lib.uh.edu/index.php?p=collections/controlcard&id=581
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Scope and Contents
This collection is predominantly comprised of documents related to Betty Jukes’ nearly fifty years as an event planner, philanthropist, and volunteer in Houston. Organizations of note that Mrs. Jukes was involved with include the Houston Junior Woman’s Club, The Woman’s Club of Houston, the Charles A. Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh Fund, and more. Spanning the years of 1967 through 2014, this collection also includes various awards and ephemera that Betty Jukes received throughout her career, and many interesting letters of correspondence between Mrs. Jukes and persons of note such as Lady Bird Johnson and Ima Hogg. Items are filed according to organizational affiliation and year.
Detailed List of Contents
- Woman's Clubs of Houston, id163707
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains materials related to the First Junior Woman’s Club of Houston, the Houston Junior Woman’s Club, and the Woman’s Club of Houston.
  - Junior Woman's Clubs, id163761
    - First Junior Woman's Club of Houston, id163763
      - First Junior Woman's Club of Houston Invitations and Newsletters, 1967-1969; id163766 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Houston Junior Woman's Club, id163764
      - Reports, 1966-1970; id163770 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Notes, 1967-1969; id163771 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1970; id163772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Minutes, 1967-1969; id163773 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Membership Lists, 1967-1970; id163774 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Organizational Papers, 1967; id163775 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - By-Laws and Constitution, 1967-1996; id163776 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Newsletters, 1968-1969; id163777 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1979; id163778 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Creative Living/Miss Wheelchair America, 1972; id163779 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Newsletters, 1974-1977; id163780 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Programs, 1967-1979; id163781 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Newsletters, 1978-1979; id163782 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Programs, 1980-1985; id163783 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Newsletters, 1980-1981; id163784 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Newsletters, 1982-1983; id163785 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Newsletters, 1984; id163786 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Newsletters, 1985-1989; id163787 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1989; id163788 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Invitations, 1968-1989; id163789 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Programs, 1986-1992; id163790 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Newsletters, 1990-1991; id163791 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Newsletters, 1992-1993; id163792 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Newsletters, 1994-1995; id163793 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Newsletters, 1996-1997; id163794 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Newsletters, 1998-1999; id163795 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Invitations, 1990-1999; id163796 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1990-1999; id163797 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Newsletters, 2000-2001; id163798 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Newsletters, 2002-2003; id163799 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Newsletters, 2004-2005; id163800 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Newsletters, 2006-2007; id163801 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Newsletters, 2008-2009; id163802 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Newsletters, 2010-2011; id163803 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Invitations, 2000-2014; id163804 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2014; id163805 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Press Releases, 1967; id163806 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Publicity, 1968-1999; id163807 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Speeches and Miscellaneous, 1968-1999; id163808 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Programs - Other, 1968-2009; id163809 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Response Cards and Blank Forms, 1973-1992; id163810 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Blank Letterheads and Envelopes, undated; id163811 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Ephemera, 1974-2002; id163812 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Press Kit, 1968; id163813 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Photos, 1968-2001; id163814 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Event Programs and Cookbooks, 1967-2009; id163815 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - The Woman's Club of Houston, id163762
    - Correspondence, 1968-1975; id163819 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Press, 1921-1980; id163820 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Programs, 1968-1994; id163821 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Invitations, 1968-1979; id163822 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Newsletters, 1968-1979; id163823 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1992; id163824 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters, 1970-1975; id163825 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Invitations, 1970-1975; id163826 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Newsletters, 1976-1978; id163827 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Newsletters, 1978-1980; id163828 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 1980-1990; id163829 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters, 1980-1983; id163830 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters, 1981-1984; id163831 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Newsletters, 1984-1987; id163832 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Newsletters, 1988-1989; id163833 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Newsletters, 1991-1992; id163834 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 1991-2000; id163835 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994; id163836 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Newsletters, 1993-1996; id163837 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 1990-2000; id163838 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1990-2000; id163839 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Newsletters, 1997-1999; id163840 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2014; id163841 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Newsletters, 2003-2005; id163842 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 2004-2014; id163843 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Newsletters, 2006-2014; id163844 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Newsletters, 2010-2014; id163845 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Financials, 1974-2014; id163846 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Member Lists and Sign-Up Sheets, 1974-2014; id163847 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Bios and Resumes, 1974-2014; id163848 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Calendars, 1974-2014; id163849 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - By-Laws and Rules, 1974-2014; id163850 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1974-2014; id163851 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Membership Forms, 1974-2014; id163852 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Notes, 1974-2014; id163853 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Awards and Miscellaneous, 1974-2014; id163854 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Scenarios and Agendas, 1974-2014; id163855 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Press, 1974-2014; id163856 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1974-2014; id163857 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Texas Federation of Women's Clubs, 1974-2014; id163858 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Texas Clubwoman Magazines and Newsletters, 1974-2014; id163859 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - General Federation of Women's Clubs Magazine and Reports, 1974-2014; id163860 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Photos, 1974-2014; id163861 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Junion Sorosis - Florida, 1967; id163862 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Houston Town and Country Magazine (Press), 1973-1976; id163863 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Legal Paperwork and Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1973-1975; id163864 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - The Woman's Club of Houston and Houston Junior Woman's Club Yearbooks, id163865 (Box 6, Item 1)
- Environmental Conservation Philanthropic Work, id163708
  This series contains materials from activities related to the Charles A. Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh Fund, an organization that funds scientific grants focused on environmental conservation and technological innovation. Also included here are Jukes’ files related to the Mercury Seven scholarship fund and the 1982 World Wildlife Foundation of Houston’s dinner honoring His Royal Highness Prince Philip of England.
  - Charles A. Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh Fund, id163868
    - Correspondence, 1977; id163895 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1983; id163896 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, January-May 1984; id163897 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, June-December 1984; id163898 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Newsletters, 1977-1999; id163899 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Invitations, Response Cards, and Tickets, 1977-1985; id163900 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Programs, 1977-1984; id163901 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1977-1985; id163902 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Invitations, Response Cards, and Tickets, 1986-2014; id163903 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1990; id163904 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1991-2014; id163905 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - James and Ellie Newton Correspondence, 1983-1999; id163906 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters, 2000-2005; id163907 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Newsletters, 2006-2010; id163908 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Financial Reports, 1977-2014; id163909 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Grant Information, 1977-2014; id163910 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Notes and Bio Sheets, 1977-2014; id163911 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Minutes, 1998-2003; id163912 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Promotional Pamphlets and Brochures, 1977-2014; id163913 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Event Planning Miscellanea and Receipts, 1977-1984; id163914 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Event Programs, 1977-1987; id163915 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Photos, 1977-2014; id163916 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Press and Publicity, 1938-2003; id163917 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Schedules, 1977-2000; id163918 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Aviation Newsletters, 1975-2008; id163919 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Member Lists, 1977-2005; id163920 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Rulebooks and "Welcome to Houston", 1977-2000; id163921 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Programs, 1985-2014; id163922 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Confederate Air Force, 1977; id163923 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Uncommon Friends, 1977-1999; id163924 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Miscellanea, 1986-1998; id163925 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Letterhead, id163926 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Membership Invitation Forms, 1983; id163927 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Mercury Seven Foundation, id163869
    - Correspondence, January-August 1985; id163928 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, September-December 1985; id163929 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1988; id163930 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1989-2014; id163931 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Member Lists, 1985; id163932 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Notes, 1985-2014; id163933 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Scholarship Information and Frequently Asked Questions, 1985; id163934 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Coca Cola in Space, 1985; id163935 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Proposals for M-7, 1984-1985; id163936 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 50th Presidential Inauguration Parade Informational Packets, 1975; id163937 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Biographies and Resumes, 1975-1985; id163938 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Press and Publicity, 1975-2013; id163939 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Business Cards, id163940 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Form Letters, 1986; id163941 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Schedules and Agendas, 1986; id163942 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Blank Forms, 1986; id163943 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Miscellanea, 1962-1980; id163944 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1985; id163945 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Company Informational Sheets, 1986; id163946 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Letterhead, id163947 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Legal, 1984; id163948 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Financials, 1984-1986; id163949 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Photos, 1984-1989; id163950 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - World Wildlife Foundation, id163870
    - Commercial, 1982; id163951 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1982; id163952 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases (1 of 2), 1982; id163953 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases (2 of 2), 1982; id163954 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Notes, 1982; id163955 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Security Schedules and Agendas, 1982; id163956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Menus, 1982; id163957 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 1982; id163958 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - His Royal Highness Prince Philip's Ephemera and Packet, 1982; id163959 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Hotel, 1982; id163960 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Tax Paperwork, 1982; id163961 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Member and Director Lists, 1982; id163962 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Scenarios, 1982; id163963 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Programs, 1982; id163964 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Seating Charts and Guest Lists, 1982; id163965 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - His Royal Highness, Press, 1982; id163966 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Rice University, 1982; id163967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Awards, 1982; id163968 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Reports, 1982; id163969 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Financials, 1982; id163970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Biographies, Curriculum Vitae, and Resumes, 1982; id163971 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Miscellanea, 1982; id163972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Photos, 1982; id163973 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Luncheon / Dinner Benefit Committees, id163709
  This collection has materials related to various benefit galas and luncheons that Jukes planned over the course of her career. Included here are planning materials and invitations from the Houstonians of the Year dinner and Clean Houston Proud Partners’ Luncheon.
  - Houston School for the Deaf Auxiliary Committee/Houstonians of the Year Dinner, id163875
    - Correspondence, 1975-1984; id163975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1989; id163976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Invitations, 1975-1989; id163977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Programs, 1981-1982; id163978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Programs, 1983-1984; id163979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Programs, 1985-1987; id163980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Programs, 1988-1989; id163981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Notes, 1981-1989; id163982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Financials, 1980-1984; id163983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Dinner Auction Lists and Inventories, 1981-1983; id163984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Directories, 1980-1983; id163985 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Seating Charts and Floor Plans, 1980-1983; id163986 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Scenarios and Agendas, 1970-1983; id163987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Reservations and Responses, 1981-1983; id163988 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Officer Lists and Committee Member Lists, 1981-1983; id163989 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Invitation Drafts, 1981-1983; id163990 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Reply Cards, 1981-1983; id163991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Informational Sheets and Fact Sheets, 1981; id163992 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Press and Publicity, 1983; id163993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - "The Voice" Newsletters, 1983-1984; id163994 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Miscellanea, 1981-1985; id163995 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Photos, 1975-1984; id163996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Clean Houston Proud Partners Luncheon, id163876
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985; id163998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1986; id163999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1987; id164000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1988; id164001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Newsletters, 1986-1987; id164002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Agendas and Meeting Minutes, 1986-1987; id164003 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Seating Charts, 1985-1987; id164004 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Contracts and Membership Lists, 1986-1987; id164005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 1985-1993; id164006 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Luncheon Scenarios, 1985-1987; id164007 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Scripts and Speeches, 1985-1987; id164008 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, 1985-1987; id164009 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Financials, 1985-1987; id164010 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Notes, 1985-1987; id164011 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Brochures, Flyers and Ephemera, 1984-1987; id164012 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Purchase Forms, 1984-1987; id164013 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Letterhead, 1984-1987; id164014 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Biographical Sketches and Fact Sheets, 1984-1987; id164015 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Awards and Certificates, 1985-1986; id164016 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Christmas at Courtlandt Place, 1985; id164017 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Photos, 1984-1987; id164018 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Publicity, 1984-1987; id164019 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Mayor's Proud Partners Luncheon Programs, 1985-1988; id164020 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Mayor's Proud Partners Luncheon Programs, 1989-1998; id164021 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Arts Philanthropy, id163710
  This series contains materials from the Houston Youth Symphony and Ballet, the University of Houston Moores’ School of Music Society, the West Point Cadets Glee Club Concerts, the Houston Grand Opera and the Theater Under the Stars of Houston, the Houston Symphony—Women’s Committee, and various Houston museums.
  - Houston Youth Symphony and Ballet, id163877
    - Correspondence, 1950-1983; id164025 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985; id164026 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1988; id164027 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1989; id164028 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1996; id164029 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1966-1984; id164030 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1985-1987; id164031 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1988; id164032 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1989-1991; id164033 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Reports, 1948-1968; id164034 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Newsletters, 1980-1990; id164035 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Scenarios and Agendas, 1984-1990; id164036 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 1978-1983; id164037 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 1984-1989; id164038 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 1990-1995; id164039 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1948-1998; id164040 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Financials, 1963-1986; id164041 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Financials, 1987-1999; id164042 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Concert Programs, 1980-1989; id164043 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Cultural Leader of the Year Programs, 1979-1984; id164044 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Cultural Leader of the Year Programs, 1985-1989; id164045 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Cultural Leader of the Year Programs, 1992-1993; id164046 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Cultural Leader of the Year Programs, 1990-1991; id164047 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Guest Lists (1 of 2), 1979-1989; id164048 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Guest Lists (2 of 2), 1979-1989; id164049 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Publicity and Press, 1980-1989; id164050 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases, 1987; id164051 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Blank Forms, 1980-1986; id164052 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Photos, 1985-1987; id164053 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Articles of Amendment, 1963-1989; id164054 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Fact Sheets, 1965-1985; id164055 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Biographies and Resumes/Curriculum Vitae, 1988; id164056 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Rulebooks/Handbooks, 1987-1990; id164057 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Notes, 1985-1990; id164058 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Job Descriptions and Contracts, 1985-1989; id164059 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Member Lists and Directors, and Executive Committee Lists, 1980-1987; id164060 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Miscellanea, 1984-1989; id164061 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - University of Houston, Moores School of Music Society, id163878
    - Correspondence, 1989-1996; id164064 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1997; id164065 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1998-2014; id164066 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Invitations and Response Cards, 1990-1996; id164067 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Programs, 1990-1996; id164068 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Programs, 1997-1998; id164069 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Programs, 1999-2014; id164070 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Press Folders, Packets, 1997-2014; id164071 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Financials, 1990-2009; id164072 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Fliers and Pamphlets, 1994-1997; id164073 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Business Cards, id164074 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Board Directories, 1998-2001; id164075 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Collegium Magazine and Houston Lifestyle, 1997-1999; id164076 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Guest Lists, 1982-1997; id164077 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Concert Schedules and Membership Pamphlets, 1994-2011; id164078 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Photos, undated; id164079 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Response Cards and Tickets, 1997; id164080 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Invitations, 1997-2014; id164081 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Publicity, 1978-2002; id164082 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Infrastructure Information, Fact Sheets, and Biographies, 1990-2002; id164083 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, undated; id164084 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1990-1991; id164085 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Board and Executive Committee Member Lists, 1991-1998; id164086 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Notes, 1990-2002; id164087 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Scenarios, Seating Charts, and Blank Forms, 1997; id164088 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Letterhead and Posters, 1990-2000; id164089 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Organizational Paperwork, Miscellaneous, 1991-1997; id164090 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - West Point Cadets' Glee Club Concerts, id163879
    - Houston Concert Programs, 1979-1990; id164093 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Concert Programs - Other Cities, 1983-1984; id164094 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Fact Sheets, 1979-1981; id164095 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Scenarios, Agendas, and Schedules, 1979; id164096 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Publicity and Press, 1979-1982; id164097 (Box 16, Folder 24)